Hi, in this section we will build complete calculator up step-by-step with the help of
it hard to pilot.
Each lesson in this section will focus on specific features so we can clearly see how
AI supports the entire development process, from coding and styling to testing and writing
the documentation.
So, the calculator instantly computes the result as the user enters numbers and operators.
Let's support all basic arithmetic operations, additions, abstraction, multiplication, and
division.
Using the viable mass logic and updates the display value in real time.
So, let's talk a bit about the user interface.
The design uses the center with cart layout, with a light background and white and dark
calculator cart.
We use the circular buttons to make it fresh and styled.
We use different adds and colors depending on the type of the button, is it the digit or
control button or operator.
So, we also provide a functionality to clear and backspace simple, so using can easily reset
the value if he enters the value, he can easily reset everything using this AC button.
And also user can delete the digits one by one using the backspace.
So, we also have a feature of a total sign, this button allows switching of the sign for
the current number instantly.
You can quickly get all, and if you, for example, add anything, so you see the result.
We also have a decimal and precision handling, let me just reset everything, so you can
add one decimal, so if you can try to add more decimals, it won't work, so we will block
user from it.
So, you see it support decimals even from the calculation, if we, for example, try to make
a division on mine, for example, you see the decimals supports it.
Okay, that's great.
We also input, limit the input, and do the formatting, as you mentioned.
For example, when you type a big number, we have a thousand separators space, so it's
clearly to the users that it's thousands, it's easy to read, and we also limit the maximum
number of digits to 10 digits.
It's not only the digits before decimal, it's in total, so you can in total, write the
10 digits.
And for the result, it can be much bigger number, so when you see the bigger number is
placed in total, in total, lines.
Okay, let's wrap up, so by the end of this lesson, you have a fully functional, those tested
and beautiful, styled calculator up, you will also learn how to use the items, like
you have to compile it, to speed up your development process, keep your good base, lean
how to do some fixes, write tests, documentation, implement features using different
approaches, so I think it will be really useful for you.
Okay, I will finish with my overview of the application, the build building this section,
and see you in the first lesson.